<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ServiceMilegiOne</string>
    <string name="title_activity_bottom__nav">MainActivity</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_bookings">Bookings</string>
    <string name="title_account">Account</string>
    <string name="db">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="about">About Us</string>
    <string name="partner">Be a Partner</string>
    <string name="edit">Edit Profile</string>
    <string name="signout">Sign Out</string>
    <string name="open">Open</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string name="quote">Service Milegi Everywhere</string>
    <string name="para">To get started, you must have answers to key questions about your business and its prospective customers. Answer each of the following questions completely, honestly and in no more than one or two sentences. It is important to be confident that you can substantiate your core beliefs with relevant arguments. What product or service does your business provide today? How does your business produce or provide the product or service right now? How will customers use your product or service as it exists right now? How will your business generate immediate revenue? Who are the primary clients your business will target immediately? How will you market your startup to prospective clients with the resources currently at your disposal? How are you different than your competitors right now? What secondary and tertiary client bases you will target once you\'ve achieved success with your primary base? Here\'s how I answered the questions for my company, Sizzle It! The company produces and edits sizzle reels, which are three-to-five minute promotional videos that combine video, graphics, photos, audio, and messaging for fast-paced, stylized product overviews. A team of freelance editors edits together media materials submitted by its clients. Customers use to offer their clients overviews of products, services or brands. It produces revenue by charging these clients flat fees for editorial services. The primary clients are boutique public-relations firms. Marketing efforts includes cold calls, search engine optimization and networking at public-relations industry events. Unlike its diversified competitors that offer large service rosters, the company will focus only on producing sizzle reels. The company will expand its client roster to include advertising agencies and small businesses.</string>
    <string name="aboutus">Key Points Economic value added suggests that a principal challenge for a business is balancing the interests of new parties affected by the business, interests that are sometimes in conflict with one another. Alternate definitions state that a business’ principal purpose is to serve the interests of a larger group of stakeholders, including employees, customers, and even society as a whole. Many observers hold that concepts such as economic value added are useful in balancing profit -making objectives with other ends. Social progress is an emerging theme for businesses. It is integral for businesses to maintain high levels of social responsibility. Key Terms corporation: A group of individuals, created by law or under authority of law, having a independent of the existences of its members, and powers and liabilities distinct from those of its members. stakeholder: A person or organization with a legitimate interest in a given situation, action, or enterprise. corporate social responsibility .</string>
</resources>